<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
    <RPP_Research_Fundamentals.label>Robotics: Fundamentals</RPP_Research_Fundamentals.label>
    <RPP_Research_Fundamentals.description>Investigation into the basic principles of robotics and automation.</RPP_Research_Fundamentals.description>
    <RPP_Research_Matrix_Basic.label>Robotics: Basic Logic</RPP_Research_Matrix_Basic.label>
    <RPP_Research_Matrix_Basic.description>Investigation into the production of the Basic Robotic Matrix units used in producing amateur-class robots. Unlocks Basic robotic research (Tier 2) and the Basic Robotic Matrix.</RPP_Research_Matrix_Basic.description>
    <RPP_Research_Cleaner_Basic.label>Robotics: Basic Cleaner</RPP_Research_Cleaner_Basic.label>
    <RPP_Research_Cleaner_Basic.description>Production of a simple cleaning robot.</RPP_Research_Cleaner_Basic.description>
    <RPP_Research_Hauler_Basic.label>Robotics: Basic Hauler</RPP_Research_Hauler_Basic.label>
    <RPP_Research_Hauler_Basic.description>Production of a simple hauling robot.</RPP_Research_Hauler_Basic.description>
    <RPP_Research_Builder_Basic.label>Robotics: Basic Builder</RPP_Research_Builder_Basic.label>
    <RPP_Research_Builder_Basic.description>Production of amateur-class, Tier 1 Builder robots becomes possible. These low-speed robots are capable of construction, deconstruction, repairing, and mining.</RPP_Research_Builder_Basic.description>
    <RPP_Research_Crafter_Basic.label>Robotics: Basic Crafter</RPP_Research_Crafter_Basic.label>
    <RPP_Research_Crafter_Basic.description>Production of amateur-class, Tier 1 Crafter robots becomes possible. These low-speed robots are capable of some tailoring, smithing, and crafting. </RPP_Research_Crafter_Basic.description>
    <RPP_Research_ER_Basic.label>Robotics: Basic ER</RPP_Research_ER_Basic.label>
    <RPP_Research_ER_Basic.description>Production of amateur-class, Tier 1 Emergency Responce robots becomes possible. These low-speed robots are capable of treating patients and fighting fires.</RPP_Research_ER_Basic.description>
    <RPP_Research_Kitchen_Basic.label>Robotics: Basic Kitchen</RPP_Research_Kitchen_Basic.label>
    <RPP_Research_Kitchen_Basic.description>Production of amateur-class Kitchen robots becomes possible.  These low-speed robots are capable of some plant work along with cooking simple meals.</RPP_Research_Kitchen_Basic.description>
    <RPP_Research_Matrix_Interm.label>Robotics: Intermediate Logic</RPP_Research_Matrix_Interm.label>
    <RPP_Research_Matrix_Interm.description>Investigation into the production of the Intermediate Robotic Matrix units used in producing professional-class robots. Unlocks Intermediate robotic research (Tier 2) and the Intermediate Robotic Matrix unit. All robots in this tier are faster and less flammable than the previous.</RPP_Research_Matrix_Interm.description>
    <RPP_Research_Builder_Interm.label>Robotics: Intermediate Builder</RPP_Research_Builder_Interm.label>
    <RPP_Research_Builder_Interm.description>Production of professional-class, Tier 2 Builder robots becomes possible. These medium-speed robots are capable of construction, deconstruction, repairing, and mining.</RPP_Research_Builder_Interm.description>
    <RPP_Research_Crafter_Interm.label>Robotics: Intermediate Crafter</RPP_Research_Crafter_Interm.label>
    <RPP_Research_Crafter_Interm.description>Production of professional-class, Tier 2 Crafter robots becomes possible. These medium-speed robots are capable of most tailoring, smithing, and crafting.</RPP_Research_Crafter_Interm.description>
    <RPP_Research_ER_Interm.label>Robotics: Intermediate ER</RPP_Research_ER_Interm.label>
    <RPP_Research_ER_Interm.description>Production of professional-class, Tier 2 Emergency Responce robots becomes possible. These medium-speed robots are capable of treating patients and fighting fires.</RPP_Research_ER_Interm.description>
    <RPP_Research_Kitchen_Interm.label>Robotics: Intermediate Kitchen</RPP_Research_Kitchen_Interm.label>
    <RPP_Research_Kitchen_Interm.description>Production of professional-class, Tier 2 Kitchen robots becomes possible.  These medium-speed robots are capable of most plant work along with cooking simple and fine meals.</RPP_Research_Kitchen_Interm.description>
    <RPP_Research_Matrix_Adv.label>Robotics: Advanced Logic</RPP_Research_Matrix_Adv.label>
    <RPP_Research_Matrix_Adv.description>Investigation into the production of the Advanced Robotic Matrix units used in producing master-class robots. Unlocks advanced robotic research (Tier 3) and the Advanced Robotic Matrix unit. All robots in this tier are faster and less flammable than the previous.</RPP_Research_Matrix_Adv.description>
    <RPP_Research_Builder_Adv.label>Robotics: Advanced Builder</RPP_Research_Builder_Adv.label>
    <RPP_Research_Builder_Adv.description>Production of Master-class, Tier 3 Builder robots becomes possible. These high-speed robots are capable of construction, deconstruction, repairing, and mining.</RPP_Research_Builder_Adv.description>
    <RPP_Research_Crafter_Adv.label>Robotics: Advanced Crafter</RPP_Research_Crafter_Adv.label>
    <RPP_Research_Crafter_Adv.description>Production of Master-class, Tier 3 Crafter robots becomes possible. These high-speed robots are capable of most tailoring, smithing, and crafting.</RPP_Research_Crafter_Adv.description>
    <RPP_Research_ER_Adv.label>Robotics: Advanced ER</RPP_Research_ER_Adv.label>
    <RPP_Research_ER_Adv.description>Production of Master-class Emergency Responce, Tier 3 robots becomes possible. These high-speed robots are capable of treating patients and fighting fires.</RPP_Research_ER_Adv.description>
    <RPP_Research_Kitchen_Adv.label>Robotics: Advanced Kitchen</RPP_Research_Kitchen_Adv.label>
    <RPP_Research_Kitchen_Adv.description>Production of Master-class, Tier 3 Kitchen robots becomes possible. These high-speed robots are capable of most plant work along with cooking simple, fine, and lavish meals.</RPP_Research_Kitchen_Adv.description>
    <!-- Anti-Logick
    <RPP_Research_AntiLogic.label>Robotics: NP=P Anti-Logic</RPP_Research_AntiLogic.label>
    <RPP_Research_AntiLogic.description>Break the boundaries set by existing levels of technology, understandings of logic, and the very concepts of causation. Our scientific horizons are becoming a lot more timey-wimey.</RPP_Research_AntiLogic.description>
    <RPP_Research_OmniBot.label>Robotics: OmniBot</RPP_Research_OmniBot.label>
    <RPP_Research_OmniBot.description>Production of a Godlike Tier 4 omni-talented robots becomes possible. These super-sonic-speed robots are capable of almost any task.</RPP_Research_OmniBot.description>
    -->
</LanguageData>
